const questionsAnswers = [
    {
        question: 'What year did Kentucky win its first national championship?',
        answers: {
            a: '1948',
            b: '1955',
            c: '1956',
            d: '1978'
        },
        correct: '1948'
    },
    {
        question: 'How many number 1 NBA draft picks does Kentucky have with John Calipari?',
        answers: {
            a: '1',
            b: '3',
            c: '5',
            d: '6'
        },
        correct: '3'
    },
    {
        question: 'How many SEC Tournament titles has Kentucky won?',
        answers: {
            a: '10',
            b: '17',
            c: '22',
            d: '31'
        },
        correct: '31'
    },
    {
        question: 'How many SEC Tournament titles have the rest of the SEC won, combined?',
        answers: {
            a: '42',
            b: '31',
            c: '25',
            d: '17'
        },
        correct: '17'
    },
    {
        question: 'How many UK players currently play in the NBA (as of the start of the 2018-19 season)?',
        answers: {
            a: '15',
            b: '28',
            c: '31',
            d: '36'
        },
        correct: '31'
    },
    {
        question: 'What building does UK play its home games in?',
        answers: {
            a: 'Memorial Hall',
            b: 'Rupp Arena',
            c: 'Memorial Collesium',
            d: 'Funkhouser Building'
        },
        correct: 'Rupp Arena'
    },
    {
        question: 'What year did Kentucky win its most recent NCAA Championship?',
        answers: {
            a: '1998',
            b: '2012',
            c: '2015',
            d: '2017'
        },
        correct: '2012'
    },
    {
        question: 'How many Final Fours has Kentucky been to?',
        answers: {
            a: '4',
            b: '12',
            c: '15',
            d: '17'
        },
        correct: '17'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which Kentucky Coach did NOT win a Championship while at Kentucky?',
        answers: {
            a: 'Billy Gillispie',
            b: 'Rick Pitino',
            c: 'John Calipari',
            d: 'Joe B. Hall'
        },
        correct: 'Billy Gillispie'
    },
    {
        question: 'How many NCAA Championships has Kentucky won?',
        answers: {
            a: '5',
            b: '7',
            c: '8',
            d: '9'
        },
        correct: '8'
    },
]